punjabpolicerecruitment.in 2017-12-26

# Punjab Police Recruitment 2016

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.   
  
**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When applying for any service or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.  
  
**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning. 

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user applying for any service, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.  
  
**Modification of Terms and Conditions of Service:**

Punjab Police may at any time modify the terms and conditions (Terms) of the Services without any prior notification to you. You can access the latest version of the Terms at any given time. You should regularly/review the Terms. In the event wherein the modified terms are not acceptable to you, you should discontinue using this website and avoid availing any services from website. However if you continue to use the service you agree to accept and abide by the modified Terms. Your use of a Site any amendment of the Terms of Use shall constitute your acceptance of these terms and you also agree to be bound by any such changes/revisions.   
  
**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

By using Punjab Police sites and services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, your only remedy is to discontinue use of Punjab Police Sites. We reserve the right, to modify this Privacy Statement at any time.   
  
**Entire Agreement**

These Terms of Service constitute the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof and supersedes and replaces.   
  
**Refund & Cancellation Policy**

The Application Form fee once deposited shall not be refunded under any circumstances.
